<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>community - Tag - Mark Cheret - Cyber Security Consultant</title><link>https://cheret.tech/tags/community/</link><description>community - Tag - Mark Cheret - Cyber Security Consultant</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under the MIT License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 21:47:52 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cheret.tech/tags/community/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Second Footnotes Community Meeting</title><link>https://cheret.tech/2021/05/second-footnotes-community-meeting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 21:47:52 +0200</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.tech/2021/05/second-footnotes-community-meeting/</guid><description>On 31/05/2021 we held our second footnotes community meeting. This time it was public! Since it&amp;rsquo;s relatively new and the meetings with the core developers happened another day due to scheduling, I was alone. Nonetheless, here&amp;rsquo;s the update:
What we talked about I screen-shared the First Footnotes Community Meeting Post and went through the kind of people we&amp;rsquo;re looking for to further enhance the plugin Version 3.0 will be coming soon The settings menu will receive a considerable overhaul further stability improvements Next footnotes community meeting The next meeting will be held on 31/05/2021 at 8pm GMT+02:00 (CET) and all following meetings will be held on the last Monday of the month at the same time.</description></item><item><title>First Footnotes Community Meeting</title><link>https://cheret.tech/2021/04/first-footnotes-community-meeting/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 21:47:52 +0200</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.tech/2021/04/first-footnotes-community-meeting/</guid><description>On 27/04/2021 we held our first footnotes community meeting. This time it was more or less an internal developer/team meeting and we&amp;rsquo;re opening it up to the public!
What we talked about the journey of the footnotes core development team over the past half year, how there was a bit of a rough patch and some storming going on. Now everything is settled and we&amp;rsquo;re bug-fixing and releasing at a sustainable pace.</description></item></channel></rss>