<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>projects - Category - Mark Cheret - Cyber Security Consultant</title><link>https://cheret.tech/categories/projects/</link><description>projects - Category - Mark Cheret - Cyber Security Consultant</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under the MIT License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 10:07:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cheret.tech/categories/projects/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>footnotes support</title><link>https://cheret.tech/footnotes-support/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 10:07:00 +0100</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.tech/footnotes-support/</guid><description><![CDATA[This page is about the WordPress plugin footnotes and how to receive support If you&rsquo;re reading these lines, I bet you&rsquo;re using footnotes the free WordPress plugin that a team of volunteers provides. It has been under development since 19 March 2014.
As I&rsquo;m receiving many emails to my personal or company inbox asking for support with this free plugin, I&rsquo;m letting you know how to actually receive support for the plugin at an appropriate place.]]></description></item><item><title>footnotes</title><link>https://cheret.tech/footnotes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 02:07:00 +0100</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.tech/footnotes/</guid><description>This page is about the WordPress plugin footnotes It has been under development since 19 March 2014.
footnotes aims to be the all-in-one solution for displaying an automatically generated list of references on your Page or Post. The Plugin ships with a set of defaults while also empowering you to control how your footnotes are being displayed.
footnotes gives you the ability to display well-formatted footnotes on your WordPress Pages and Posts — those footnotes we know from offline publishing.</description></item></channel></rss>