<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>All Posts - Mark Cheret - Cyber Security Consultant</title><link>https://cheret.tech/posts/</link><description>All Posts | Mark Cheret - Cyber Security Consultant</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under the MIT License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 18:50:21 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cheret.tech/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why I Renamed My Git Branches From Master to Main</title><link>https://cheret.tech/2021/05/why-i-renamed-my-git-branches-from-master-to-main/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 18:50:21 +0200</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.tech/2021/05/why-i-renamed-my-git-branches-from-master-to-main/</guid><description><![CDATA[It&rsquo;s been a while since GitHub changed the default branch name from master to main. If you&rsquo;re interested in the deeper background and how GitHub are not the only platform implementing this change, check out the statement of the &lsquo;software freedom conservancy&rsquo; on 23/6/2020.
What I welcome most about this movement is that it got way easier to rename the default branch on GitHub, which used to be a major PITA.]]></description></item><item><title>First Footnotes Community Meeting</title><link>https://cheret.tech/2021/05/first-footnotes-community-meeting/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 13:47:52 +0200</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.tech/2021/05/first-footnotes-community-meeting/</guid><description>On 27/04/2021 we held our first footnotes community meeting. This time it was more or less an internal developer/team meeting and we&amp;rsquo;re opening it up to the public!
What we talked about the journey of the footnotes core development team over the past half year, how there was a bit of a rough patch and some storming going on. Now everything is settled and we&amp;rsquo;re bugfixing and releasing at a sustainable pace.</description></item><item><title>footnotes celebrates its 7th anniversary</title><link>https://cheret.tech/2021/03/footnotes-celebrates-its-7th-anniversary/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 08:00:00 +0100</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.tech/2021/03/footnotes-celebrates-its-7th-anniversary/</guid><description>Happy 7th birthday footnotes the footnotes WordPress plugin is celebrating its 7th anniversary today. We haven&amp;rsquo;t decided as a team on what we&amp;rsquo;re going to do to celebrate this occasion together with our community. So please watch this space for announcements.</description></item><item><title>footnotes</title><link>https://cheret.tech/footnotes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 02:07:00 +0100</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.tech/footnotes/</guid><description>This page is about the WordPress plugin footnotes It has been under development since 19 March 2014.
footnotes aims to be the all-in-one solution for displaying an automatically generated list of references on your Page or Post. The Plugin ships with a set of defaults while also empowering you to control how your footnotes are being displayed.
footnotes gives you the ability to display well-formatted footnotes on your WordPress Pages and Posts — those footnotes we know from offline publishing.</description></item><item><title>my first post with a new CMS</title><link>https://cheret.tech/2021/03/my-first-post-with-a-new-cms/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 15:36:53 +0100</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.tech/2021/03/my-first-post-with-a-new-cms/</guid><description><![CDATA[after more than a decade Just so you know, I&rsquo;ve been a WordPress user, admin, and plugin author for more than a decade now. I could&rsquo;ve set this up as yet another one of those ubiquitous WordPress pages. This time, however, I&rsquo;m taking a different approach. HUGO is my tool of choice as I&rsquo;m a DevSecOps Advisor, leaning into Infrastructure as Code (IaC) and of course the automation behind this declarative setup.]]></description></item><item><title>celebrating 100k Downloads</title><link>https://cheret.tech/2021/03/celebrating-100k-downloads/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 20:47:42 +0000</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.tech/2021/03/celebrating-100k-downloads/</guid><description>This marks a point in time, where our WordPress Plugin &amp;ldquo;footnotes&amp;rdquo; received a download count of 100,000. Cheers to all who downloaded it, thanks to all who use it, thx to those seeking support and props to all contributors! Visit the WordPress Plugin Page: https://wordpress.org/plugins/footnotes/</description></item><item><title>footnotes: How to recover from a crashing website</title><link>https://cheret.tech/2021/03/footnotes-how-to-recover-from-a-crashing-website/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 02:17:42 +0100</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.tech/2021/03/footnotes-how-to-recover-from-a-crashing-website/</guid><description>Dear footnotes community,
We recently accidentally shipped a version of our plugin that might break your website. Apologising here.
How to recover from a crashing website? Fellow footnotes user @pppierreee pointed out that it would be helpful to give you guidance how to recover:
– Download footnotes 2.5.8 – Unzip – Delete the wp-content/plugins/footnotes/ folder on your webserver – Upload the contents of the unzip (the footnotes folder) to wp-content/plugins/</description></item><item><title>footnotes 2.5.10 reverts 2.5.9d1 and apologies</title><link>https://cheret.tech/2021/03/footnotes-2.5.10-reverts-2.5.9d1-and-apologies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 19:02:22 +0100</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.tech/2021/03/footnotes-2.5.10-reverts-2.5.9d1-and-apologies/</guid><description>In the development of the WordPress plugin footnotes, we shipped a broken version that crashed websites for arond four hours starting from 08:37 am. Here is the short version. If you want to dive deeper, check out this forum post
Dear footnotes community thank you for your continued support. I’m sorry we shipped a broken version of the plugin earlier today and we reverted to a stable version with the latest update 2.</description></item><item><title>celebrating 1k Downloads</title><link>https://cheret.tech/2014/07/celebrating-1k-downloads/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2014 20:47:42 +0000</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.tech/2014/07/celebrating-1k-downloads/</guid><description><![CDATA[This marks a point in time, where our WordPress Plugin &ldquo;footnotes&rdquo; received a download count of 1000. Cheers to all who downloaded it, thanks to all who use it, thx to those seeking support and props to all contributors! &ldquo;We&rdquo; are Stefan and Mark and call ourselves &ldquo;Media Competence Institute&rdquo;. We sail under the flag displayed below. Visit the WordPress Plugin Page: https://wordpress.org/plugins/footnotes/]]></description></item><item><title>the all hyped up .uk top level domain</title><link>https://cheret.tech/2014/06/the-all-hyped-up-.uk-top-level-domain/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2014 20:37:08 +0000</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.tech/2014/06/the-all-hyped-up-.uk-top-level-domain/</guid><description>.uk is the Internet country code top-level domain (ccTLD) for the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland. As of March 2012, it is the fourth most popular top-level domain worldwide (after .com, .de and .net), with over 10 million registrations. Starting 10th June 2014 it is now possible to register domains ending with a plain .uk. People may have wondered for ages as to why there were only .</description></item></channel></rss>